But this doesn't end here, actually.
When it comes to photo editor, we have a pretty complete editor.
We have a just.
So these are going to be tools like crop, rotator and flip,
resize, color, fine tune, basic adjust.
For example, I open up fine tune.
And I will be able to change, for example,
the exposure of lights in my image, as you see,
as beautiful as that.
So I change it back to zero.
I can make the highlights lighter or darker.
I can also work on the shadows.
I can turn shadows lighter or darker than they are, as you see.
And what else can we do?
I can go to color and change the temperature
and tint to my image.
As you see, I can make it colder or warmer.
So I said it to zero.
We have basic adjustments, like brightness, contrast,
saturation, and sharpness.
So as you see, all of these photo editing
kind of materials are available to us using this very photo
editor.